

RAJESH KUMAR Software Developer

Bangalore

☑ rajeshkr908070@gmail.com

& 8235571164

SOCIAL

@github

in @linkedin

@stackoverflow

PROFILE

Software Developer with 2+ years of experience in various technical fields like ReactJs, Angular, JavaScript, Java, NodeJs.I have work experience in domains like Retail, Banking and Insurance, delivered projects with tight deadlines in agile way.

EDUCATION

■ BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE & ENGINEERING

KLS Gogte Institute Of Technology

2015 - 2019

® 9.5CGPA

SCIENCE - CBSE 12th Board

DAV Public School

2013 - 2014

Grade A

CBSE 10th Board

DAV Public School

2011 - 2012

® 9.8CGPA

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- React
- Html
- Angular
- CSS
- NodeJs
- Java

EXPERIENCE

SYSTEM ENGINEER | DEVELOPER

From Jul 2019 to present | Tata Consultancy Services Software Development with 2+ years of experience (React,Angular,Java,NodeJs).

SDE PROJECT INTERN

From Jan 2019 to May 2019 | Capillary Technologies
Web Development Intern (Angular, Java, Dockernetes, Kubernetes).

TELECOM NETWORKING PROJECT INTERN

From May 2017 to Jul 2017 | BSNL

Networking and Tele-Communication.

CERTIFICATES

Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals (2021)

Microsoft Azure Certification, See credential

Business English preliminary - University of Cambridge (2019)

Certified by Cambridge University for Business English.Certificate No.:0054504784

Udemy React and Java Certification (2021)

Certified by Udemy for course completion

Udemy Angular Certification (2021)

Certified by Udemy for course completion

World Intellectual Property Organization – WIPO(2019)

WIPO Intellectual Property Rights Certication. Credential ID FtiUCWNImJ

ORGANIZATIONS

Associate Member

Rotaract Club of GIT(Rotary Club)

Aug 2015 - Jul 2017
As an associate member of KLS GIT,
BELGAUM, chapter of ROTARACT CLUB OF
GIT, Involved in Traffic awareness and
Road safety projects/campaigns,
promoting and advertising students
friendly GK App(oust app) for children in
schools around Belgaum.

LANGUAGES

• English(Professional Working Proficiency) • Hindi(Native or Bilingual Proficiency)

INTEREST